alldata.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy - ALLDATA

##  ALLDATA.com Privacy Policy   
Updated May, 2013

Updated May, 2013 

**Information Collection**

When you visit ALLDATA.COM (“ALLDATA”), you can surf the site anonymously and access important information about ALLDATA’s products without revealing your identity. At times, particularly when you order products, download software, or enter contests from the ALLDATA web site, ALLDATA may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to participate in these programs. If you elect to participate in these programs, however, ALLDATA may require that you provide your contact information, which may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address or other personally identifying information. When you make purchases through our site, we may also collect your credit card information and billing address when you provide us with such information. 

When you submit personal information to ALLDATA, you understand and agree that ALLDATA and its affiliates may access, store, and use your customer profile in any of the countries in which ALLDATA and its affiliates maintain offices, including without limitation the United States. We collect this information for a variety of reasons, including ALLDATA’s effort to inform you of product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services from ALLDATA. ALLDATA recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of the information you choose to provide. If you are an ALLDATA customer, you understand and agree that you will receive email notifications, promotional messaging, newsletters and other information from ALLDATA. 

**Information Use**

When you submit personal information to ALLDATA, you understand and agree that ALLDATA and its affiliates may access, store, and use your customer profile in any of the countries in which ALLDATA and its affiliates maintain offices, including without limitation the United States. We collect this information for a variety of reasons, including ALLDATA’s effort to inform you of product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services from ALLDATA. ALLDATA recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of the information you choose to provide. If you are an ALLDATA customer, you understand and agree that you will receive email notifications, promotional messaging, newsletters and other information from ALLDATA. 

**Cookies**

The Web Site may use third party products and services to gather traffic statistics using cookies and web beacons. A cookie is a small piece of information stored with your browser that helps web sites and multiple servers recognize your browser or device. ALLDATA and its third party service providers may also use technology including pixels and transparent GIF files for purposes including web site management and customization. 

**Your Choices**

You may opt out of receiving Act-On cookies at:  

You may opt out of receiving Google Analytics cookies at:  

You may opt out of receiving CoreMotives cookies at:  
<http://coremotives.com/privacy-statement> or  
<http://www.ibm.com/privacy/us/en/>

**Contact Us**

By using this site, you agree to the terms of the ALLDATA Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use this site. ALLDATA is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-ALLDATA web sites to which alldata.com or any other ALLDATA web site may link. 

Copyright © 1996-2013 ALLDATA LLC. All rights reserved. 

**R053113**
